temp-mail.org 2019-12-12

# Privacy policy & Terms of use

**1\. Privacy policy**  
last updated 24 may 2018

Temp-mail.org is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect lawfully in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).

Information is saved for many years on your conventional e-mail. This may be exposed to hacking or lost due to failure of service.

Using the temporary mail allows you to completely protect your real mailbox against the loss of personal information. Your temporary e-mail adress is completely anonymous. Your details: information about your person and users with whom you communicate, IP-address, e-mail address are protected and completely confidential.

Temp Mail Service does not store your IP-address. This means you are reliably protected from all unauthorised actions that may endanger your information and compromise your privacy. All emails and data temporarily stored on our service are permanently deleted after 25 minutes. You can delete your temporary Email address at any time using the appropriate button 'Delete' on the home page.

Your privacy is the highest priority for us. You need not concern yourself about your data. We will provide full protection. Access to your data will only be provided to you personally and only for the lifetime of the temporary email address.

**What information do we collect?**

No personal data is collected. Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and remember certain information.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites.

Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting [Ads Settings.](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).)

If you have not [opted out of third-party ad serving](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94152), the cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://support.google.com/dfp_sb/answer/94149) may also be used to serve ads on your site, which should also be disclosed in your privacy policy in the following manner:

* Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site.

* Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites.

* Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendors’ uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) for guidance on drafting a privacy policy. For additional details regarding cookie consent notices, please refer to [cookiechoices.org](http://cookiechoices.org/).

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Third Party Ad Companies**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**2\. Terms of service**

By using this service, you agree to the following terms: Temp-mail.org. makes no warranty of reliability or suitability for any purpose. Its availability or existence may be removed at any time by its owners. Any email sent through Temp-mail.org may or may not be available for viewing, may be altered, and is immediately viewable by ANY user of the system. You agree to only access Temp-mail.org data through the Temp-mail.org website or Temp-mail.org-provided facilities (i.e. Temp-mail.org-mobile). Programmatic access is limited to paid accounts and the provided API. You agree to not use Temp-mail.org directly or indirectly for any unlawful purpose. You agree that any email you send to Temp-mail.org or emails you induce other sites/persons to send will become public domain once in the Temp-mail.org system with no expectation of privacy for email content . You agree not to use the public Temp-mail.org system to receive, store, or view emails containig private or confidential information. You understand that Temp-mail.org has no control over material put into mailboxes. You agree to hold Temp-mail.org harmless from any damages caused by loss of emails, content within emails, damage to your computer (or innocence) from viewing emails, direct or indirect use of this system.
